# **Bhavesh Shahani**

## JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER

🔀 gudd.shahani@gmail.com

in BhaveshShahani\_LinkedIn

BhaveshShahani\_Github

BhaveshShahani\_Twitter

▶ BhaveshShahani\_Portfolio



#### **EDUCATION**

## **Java Developer**

Masai School Apr 2022 – Present | Bangalore, India

## **Senior Secondary Education**

Sanmati School May 2016 | Indore

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JAVA | SPRING BOOT | MAVEN | HIBERNATE SQL | JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS | DSA

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Store Manager**

*Mithi Mirchi Cafe* 2019 – 2020 | Indore Worked as a Store Manager.

#### **Sales Manager**

*DAYA WorldWide PVT. LTD.* 2017 – 2019 | Indore Worked as a Sales Manager.

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Diploma In Event Managment

JAVA Basic HackerRank

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Team Work | Problem Solving | Motivated

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Developer with knowledge of technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Able to learn new technologies and software. Have an experience of 1000+ hours of Coding and Data Structure Algorithms. Team player who provides valuable support in a team environment.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Bus Reservation Rest\_API**

#### **Project Link**

Rest\_API using Spring Boot.

#### **Tech-Stack**

Java | SpringBoot | SQL | Hibernate | Swagger.

#### Responsibility

Feedback Section

## Bewakoof Clone

Website

Bewakoof is a lifestyle fashion brand that makes creative, distinctive fashion for the trendy, contemporary Indian.

#### **Tech-Stack**

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

### Responsibility

Product Page Design | Sorting

\_\_\_\_\_

## **Bath And Body Works Clone**

Website

Bath & Body Work is an online eCommerce cosmetic brand, Which is a retail store chain that sells soaps, lotions, fragrances, and candles.

#### **Tech-Stack**

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

#### Responsibility

Team Lead | Layout of the website | Merging